Frank wasn't a mole from Dallas I have no
Frank no era topo de Dallas yo no tengo
problem with Frank I like him I saw his
problema con Frank me cae bien vi sus
videos I think he's talked a lot about me
videos creo que ha hablado mucho de mí
without knowing me when he meets me we'll
sin conocerme cuando me conozca vamos a
see if he says the same thing to have an opinion that one
ver si habla lo mismo opinar que una
person raped another is something very hard
persona violó a otra es algo muy duro
very raw and I clearly know how
muy crudo y yo claramente sé cómo son
things are and all the people who know me
las cosas y toda la gente que me conoce
also know it It makes me sad that a
también sabe Me pone triste que una
person like him who I don't like at all His
persona como él que yo Nada me gusta Su
content and I like the message he gives and
contenido y me gusta el mensaje que da y
what he does has that opinion about me but I
lo que hace opine eso sobre mí pero yo
have no problem I would love to help
no tengo problema Me encantaría ayudar
with the cause I would love for him to recover
con la causa Me encantaría que recuper
from his sanctuary let's see regarding ccu
de su santuario a ver respecto a ccu lo
what happens is that it's not only that
que pasa es que no es únicamente aquel
episode because that episode even
episodio porque aquel episodio incluso
if it were an isolated incident of one day where you
si fuera un hecho aislado de un día que
put your foot in it I think that here who more
metes la pata yo creo que aquí quien más
and who less maybe not at that level
y quien menos a lo mejor no en ese nivel
obviously not but you put your foot in it and
evidentemente no pero la pata la metes y
you're wrong the problem with cocu is that
te equivocas el problema de cocu Es que
then he has other episodes like the one with
luego tiene otros episodios como el de
caprim min there you say you [ __ ] you have a
caprim min ahí dices tú [__] tienes
certain tendency over time to
cierta tendencia a lo largo del tiempo a
certain behaviors that it may be that
unos comportamientos que puede ser que
you have been raised in an environment in which you
te hayas criado en un ambiente en el que
have normalized it that you  You start
lo tengas normalizado que te pones a
denying it and of course the more you deny it they
negarlo y claro Cuanto más lo niegues te
will tell you that it is not that it is that this is how it is that
van a decir que no es que es que esto es
you have a live where you make
así es que tienes un directo donde haces
this comment where you make this other
este comentario donde haces este otro
comment the photo according to ccu is this one
comentario la foto según ccu es esta